{
    "id": "334ac5cb7833427fa0269db3804c1080",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Give me something to drink, or …………….. I will die of thirst.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "else",
                "otherwise"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. you are mistaken or I am.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Either",
                "Neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He asked …………………. he might have something to eat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "weather",
                "whether",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. you are called, you must come in at once.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "When",
                "While"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I cannot give you any money ………………. I have none.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "that",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You will not succeed ………………. you work harder.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless",
                "weather"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He fled ………………. he should be killed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "lest",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We started early ………………… we will not get stuck in the traffic.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so that",
                "such that",
                "such as"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He deserves to succeed …………….. he works hard.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "because",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I hear ………………… your brother is in China.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}